and And we are back on the ship ship
show. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
>> Welcome. Welcome.
[laughter]
>> How you doing?
>> How is it here? It's hot here. We
finally have the summer in Netherlands.
>> True. Oh, yeah. I mean, yeah, it's hot
since winter, so
>> Yeah. I'm not living on the beach, so
a tropical island.
>> Yeah. I mean, oh, like a tax seven
island. [laughter]
>> Well, that's what we need, right?
Because we're going to build.
>> We need money first.
>> Oh, yeah. But AI is going to give us
money.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what everybody does.
>> I high I basic comrate.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh Yeah. Until then, we still need to
stream.
>> Yeah. So, here we are again.
>> Here we are again. one more week and
yeah, it's like uh 16 episode. That's
good. Like uh the the crowd is in is
crazy, but that's okay. That's okay. We
manage.
>> Yeah. So, if you're here and have
questions, let us know
>> and subscribe and come back next week.
Thank you.
>> Yes.
>> But yeah, let's uh talk about curs. The
ID that nobody use, but at least we can
use the model now. So, there's that.
That's there's the story behind Yeah.
Koso is interesting for sure. No,
because I was was white.
>> So, please tell me because I don't know.
>> Okay. Okay. So, I'm going to do an
introduction and then uh let's go
>> then let's go.
>> Okay.
>> Are you still using cursor? Yes. Uh or
not? Maybe not because cloud code is now
more used by every Y at YC and every
developer in the world. So if you don't
maybe you don't know there is like
composer 2.5 that is probably the best
model out there right now. So if you
don't use cursor that's probably a
mistake isn't it Mitchell?
>> Yeah I made the biggest mistake then.
>> Yeah but we're gonna talk about that
right now and see if it's true or not.
But composer 2.5 it's cheap way cheaper
than um OPUS. It's way faster than Opus
and Codex all together. And uh it's B
but it's also but and it's based on the
Chinese open source model. So that's
also interesting.
>> Well, yeah, the naming got me wrong
>> because I'm using composer
for the last few years and it it wasn't
AI. [snorts]
>> But now they have the same name as
composer for installing all the
dependencies.
>> Ah yeah, for PHP, right? That composer.
Yeah, it's the npm of uh PHP.
>> Yes.
>> Do you get hacked every week?
>> Nope. [snorts]
I I even didn't get hacked at the last
one.
>> Damn. Good job.
>> That's That's good.
>> Yeah, good job.
>> Clients, if you are safe, [laughter]
>> you are safe. We don't update that many
times because we check everything up
front.
>> Nice.
Really good practice now.
>> Yeah. But that was just a small
flashback to last week.
>> Yeah. And yeah, by the way, if you
haven't watched the video, if you
haven't watched the live stream or if
you didn't see any short, please do. Uh,
we need watch time. So, enjoy the
security live stream on the YouTube
channel.
>> If you want your code to be secure,
please watch it.
>> Yeah. Oh, switch from JavaScript to PHP.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, not at this time, but
>> Oh,
>> I think we have a second composer now.
And apparently that's for cursor.
>> Yes. Yes, sir. So, cursor. Bam. Demo
share screen.
[snorts]
Let's go bigger. Blah blah blah blah
blah. Wow. Uh, introducing composer 2.5.
That was that was that was that was on
the 18.
Where did I lost? Oh, no. Yeah. 18 18.
There's the date in the middle of it of
the title.
>> Yeah. So, yeah. less than 10 8 days ago.
Uh cursor launch composer 2.5 uh is now
available at incursor and only available
in cursor. You can't target it on open
router. It's a sub substant substantial
it's a substantial improvement in
intelligence in behavior over composer
2. It's it is better at sustain work uh
on a long running task. Follows complex
instruction more reiable
follows complex instruction more real
[laughter]
follows better.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> More pleasant to collaborate with I I
don't care about that. Like I don't
>> listen
>> and be smart.
>> Yeah, exactly. Like just do what the
[__] I want and fix my bug.
>> Yes.
>> Like Okay. Yeah. Whatever. Um we Okay.
So yeah, which is interesting. Terminal
Bench 2. 2.0 which is like the CLI um
benchmark.
>> Mhm.
>> Opus 4.7 69 and Composer 69.3. And Opus
is at4.
>> That's nice.
>> GPT 5.582
and Composer 261. So yeah. Oh, GPT5 82.
Oh
>> yeah. Yeah. I like GPT 5.5.
>> Damn.
>> So well I think that's why they compare
with Opus.
>> Yes. [laughter]
>> Not with codeex.
>> Um so bench multiling multilingual uh
79.8
8 Opus 80
GPT5 77 see
>> yeah and 73 so yeah 6 point more for
than composer 2 and a cursor bench
internal I guess internal uh benchmark
63 64 64 60.8 8 64.3 for CEX 52. Yeah,
that's good. 10 point uh we improve
composer by scaling training generating
more complex um error
>> real life
>> rec no recursive learning [laughter]
>> right
I mean I think
>> re real life reduce level oh
reinforcement learning yeah not
recursive reinforcement learning my bad
uh in addition to training composer 2.5
on more difficult task improve beveral
aspect of the model like communications
communication style and effort
calibration like me but like I need to
use composer 2.5 uh oh GM noise thank
you for that uh these dimension are not
well captured by existing benchmark but
we find that they're made more for real
real world userfulness
yeah so of course they they have created
their own benchmark and they are like
top right
>> yeah well I I think that's always
stupid.
>> Yeah,
>> because if you create your own
benchmark, you're not going to lose on
it, right?
>> Exactly. So that that's why like we have
other benchmark from uh where is it?
Where do I have it? Uh I have another
one
from uh where is the article?
Where is it?
Yes. artificial analysis coding tech
share this one that that's gonna be
that's gonna be something else like the
the jump is not the same like okay so
that's a composer too but uh it's a good
jump but still behind clude code and GPT
but uh way cheaper so that's interesting
uh shista bum uh composer uh 85% of the
compute of composer 2.5 Five comes from
additional training and reinforcement
learning uh composer training and
reinforcement. That's basically every
action that it's going through cursor
[clears throat]
>> they are putting in on top of the uh
model. So basically what they do is
fine-tune
um Kimmy 2.5 and make it better with all
of the developer data they have from the
ID. And that's why Ellen Musk bought or
uh put an option on cursor because all
of that data can be used on gro.
>> Yeah, they have people paying them to
get a subscription to help them train
their own model.
>> Wait, they have other people paying them
to train their Yes.
>> Yeah, that's smart, right?
>> I mean, that's good.
>> I have a product. We can make it better.
Please pay me to do it. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Basically like together with
basics we have trained a significant
larger model from scratch using 10x more
total compute. Yeah. Colorus 2 millions
H
with corus to minion H100 equivalent and
our combined data of training technique.
We expect this to be a major leap in
model capability which is also exposed
um on Elon Musk account. Mhm.
>> Alon
I don't need to search a lot on
uh Grog foundation model V9 medium 1.5
trillion parameter has finished training
a looks good a lot of cursor data was
added in supplementary training and
there is more to come so
that that's this one could be really
interesting to see how it goes after
that but I I think they could leap frog
a lot but still like it will take time
for them to catch up with glow and opus
I think.
>> Yeah that's true but if he keeps putting
in the money and the effort they can
scale fast
>> especially if they have colossus because
then they have the energy and then you
can increase the
yeah all of the parameters and all of
the like training of the model. Mhm.
>> Just curious what's what's in the cursor
data. This means the upcoming rock model
will be much better at coding. Much
better. Yeah. Imagine he replied, "No,
no, it's not going to be that good."
[laughter]
>> He just wouldn't reply. That's bad.
>> Uh, okay. Yeah. Back to composer because
all of that it's kind of linked all
together. That's interesting. Uh,
training 2.5 contains several new
improvement to our training stack. this
changes target post model intelligence
and usability
uh yeah textual feedback
we care about that I don't think so
textual feedback insert target and int
to learn correction
pass
okay
and m okay okay okay I'm not going to
read that we need we need watch type
>> so yeah Try composite 2.5.
>> But this is cheap.
>> See that? Yes.
>> Like the the the the 50 cents and $25
that's cheap.
>> Yeah. Like uh
>> other models are at least a 10x ones.
>> Seven.
Uh pricing API 5 million. Yeah. Five
bucks.
>> Yeah. That's a 10x.
>> Uh one cash right cash output token 25.
Yeah. Then the only question is in the
other overview. Why would you use Opus
4.1 at triple pricing?
>> Yeah, because we have a subscription.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean that that's and I guess like you
can get it for in the 25 bucks, right?
Pricing. Yeah. 20.
Yeah. [__] That's another 200. Access
to frontier model MCP cloud agent
work boat on usage base. Yeah, that's
crazy. Like that's another 40 bucks a
month.
>> So that's annoying. Uh price access to
new feature. Okay, cool. Uh where's the
team enterprise? Yeah,
I mean, yeah, but I mean it could be
I know you have access Yeah, you have
access to all of the frontier models. So
even if you take like the subscription
in cursor, you can have access to all
the models.
>> Mhm.
>> You just Yeah.
But yeah. Uh so yeah, what's the current
usage of cursor right now? Like
>> mine?
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> it's zero. Yeah,
>> I I skipped it because um I was finally
used to the layout and I'm doing almost
all of my work in terminal.
>> Yeah.
>> In the CLI and then they came with the
agent uh layout and I just had to start
over and I really like working in the
CLI. So also switching the models it's
so much easier in CLI. So I just kept
using the CLI and I dumped cursor.
>> H yeah. I I think like when everyone
switched to cloud code it was when they
launch
4.5 even better even before. No.
>> Yeah. Before but
>> yeah even before but um and everyone
went to the CLI back to the CLI.
>> Yes
>> that's that that was crazy. That was
>> and that it works perfectly. Yeah, I I
watch like yeah theo video and he said
that yeah like cursor went to so all of
the startup at YC use cursor like 90% of
the company were were using cursor
>> and in the next batch went to 70% clo
code
>> yeah and they can say they have all the
models in it but
>> still
>> yeah and then there there is like the uh
curs our glass stuff. I think it's
another ID and it's more like a back to
T3 codes UI.
Uh I'm curious about their product line.
What do they have now? Because Yeah, I'm
just using Yeah, see that? Oh, yeah.
Okay. So, they reorganized that to be
even more like just aentic. No more
editor. See, they're not they're not
even showing the code anymore.
>> Yeah. That's why people are using the
CLI because nobody is watching the code
produced by the agent except in the pull
request.
>> Yeah, I want to see what it does during
the changes as well.
>> Yeah,
>> because sometimes it still does really
weird stuff,
>> bro. Like I I I told you before the
show, but like I got completely [__]
this weekend like crazy. So quickly uh I
had the so I I migrated like the project
from [__] to postgrql
>> and clude put a okay what
[laughter]
>> it
so I was doing the migration from [__]
to postgresq
>> mh
>> then at some point I I didn't take uh I
didn't uh I I don't know why but clothes
stash the some card on the side and I
didn't notice it
and then two three days after that. So
but yeah basically Sunday um
I found those stash code and and I asked
what the [__] is that? What happened
with that? Uh do we mig should we put
back all of that code in the current
work?
and CL told me yes because there's some
valuable stuff blah blah blah
>> I migrated I worked again on some agent
on the side in parallel and then more
commits blah blah blah five more commits
on top of it and then I go to test the
app and then nothing work everything is
broken I say what's going on it was not
like that before like this features was
done like three days ago why not here I
say oh yeah blah blah blah Um
what did you do with the stash branch? I
said oh yeah it was the migration from
three days ago that so I had a mix of
the migration that's been done from
[__] to posgrsql plus some task that I
wanted to do next. So I could not roll
back without losing those commits. So I
I started to fix everything
and then 10 commit later like I was
going nowhere and I had regression after
regression and I didn't want to lose
what I've done because I would have have
to track what I've lost. So I just
continue and it took me like 20 hours to
just fix this dash migration without
losing anything. Not crazy. And this is
a moment you can't tell cloud code fix
it because it will just keep on looping
and keep making mistakes
>> completely lost. So one by one like
commit after commit or page after page I
say okay uh this one was not like that
yesterday fix it.
>> Yeah
>> pro it's probably in this commit and
then close. Oh yes exactly we we deleted
25 files. Yeah.
>> Yes. [laughter] So yeah, but like I
should have paid attention better. But
uh that's why more ID and terminal looks
like that because nobody's watching the
cut except you because you produce
quality software.
>> Yeah. But also small parts, just small
branches, small changes and not like hey
here is a full list of changes I need to
everything at once.
>> Yeah. I know. Exactly. Uh, like I I
think with AI and orchestration that's
even more true than ever. Like you
really need to build uh a skateboard and
then a bike and then a car and then a
[__] rocket. And I have used to just
build like too much [__] and have like a
crazy scope every comet. I need to stop
that because that's exactly what
happened with uh with CL. And also I
didn't work with walk trees. Everything
was on the same branch because it was
supposed to be a small update
>> and uh then close started to create a
branch. So the state of the code was
[__] and so all of the agent like the
five six agent I had running at the same
time got completely lost and then they
were rewriting each other.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I know it. It's that's it's
bad because it's so hard to then figure
out where to start, what to fix because
once you find an issue and you think you
fixed it, you broke something different.
>> Like I I spent like the 20 20 20 hours
fixing that and no sleep.
>> Yeah,
>> that was a problem. But uh
>> fun times with cloud code.
>> Yes. And no, I need to try composer 2.5.
>> But are you using cursor as well next to
your CLI? So I'm just using cursor to
check the state of my pull request and
my branches and to see if there is any
work trees that I'm not aware of it
because I need to visualize that them
but uh yeah like looks like everything
is cursor I don't know
>> I don't yeah I don't use but I use all
the software maybe I should go back to
cursor like I'm using like T3 codes but
like in the last few days it was not
working properly neither so I went back
to code like from Entropic and Codex for
for Codex
>> Mhm.
>> OpenAI. I went to the OG's OG's apps. Uh
and it's kind of cool like it's it's way
nicer than a terminal for me. But um
yeah, there is always some features that
are missing that you can only find in an
open source project because then
everyone is adding the same features
like for example open a pull request
from CL code. You like I don't know
where the [__] button is. Well, I you
say you're doing it in cursor, but I'm
doing all my uh branch uh checks to see
what's ready to commit to see the
changes. I'm doing that in still in the
jet brain software.
>> Oh yeah,
>> I used to work before AI came.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You already open Jetbrain to
see what's up. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But all the coding is done in the
CLI.
>> Yeah.
And what about like your pull request?
Do you send like every any AI to review
the code or you do review everything?
>> I still uh use a second screen. So it's
either codeex builded cloud code checks
it or the other way around.
>> Yeah. Okay. Do you review every line
that's produced by AI or not?
>> Um I look over it
>> and to see if I can say I just scan it
and see if I see some really weird
stuff.
>> Uh but I'm not checking every detail.
>> Yeah. Okay. Makes sense. I mean, aentic
coding, right?
>> Yeah. But if you work with functions
that you create and you just include it,
that's no problem. But if you change the
function, then you need to check it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like that's that's the
state I'm in right now. Like I'm
refactoring like I'm cleaning some
codebase and trying to make it like all
work together. And that's not a funny
state to be with like five agents
running. But again, as soon as you have
a stable codebase, then it's basically
like how you should build an open source
project, you know, with like 1,000
contributor.
>> Mhm.
>> And you have like the contributing MD is
telling you to five five files maximum
or the pull request will never be merged
and that's it.
>> Yeah, exactly. And that's what you need
to do here as well.
>> Yeah. Like for real. And uh because
basically your team is like five agents
on the same work tree/branch whatever
project. So yeah it makes sense makes
sense. You just need like some yeah
better organization from my side and
after this [__] up uh going to do
that. Uh yeah. Okay. So from artificial
analysis which is like a benchmark uh
like a better benchmark like a third
party benchmark for for for this uh
composer 2.5 which is not
cursor bench.
>> Mhm.
>> Um the last model in the composer line
uh scored 62 on our coding agent index a
40 point gain over composer 2. Let's put
it third place of all tested agents
behind only clopus max. Oh okay 4.7 max
in cl code 66. Oh okay there is a gap um
and GPT 5. XI reasoning in codec 65.
Okay.
The cost 4
uh four bucks and 10 cent and 482 per
tax respectively. 10x the cost of
composer 2.5 fast. Yeah, like
at 40 cent 44 cent and 60x the cost of
composer 2.5 standard 0.7.
>> So then my question is do cloud code and
codex have so high margins or
are they really making it so much
better? Uh, I mean you can
like the margin doesn't you can I mean
>> yeah if you if it's 60 times more
expensive to use
>> the other ones that's a lot
>> um
but maybe no like the okay no the the
point is the margin maybe like the
margin of composer 2.5 is [__]
>> you don't know that
>> you don't know therefore the question
Yeah, it needs to be somewhere.
>> Um. Oh, yeah. Because Okay. So, what you
say like if it if if they don't have
margin, then they could increase the
price and not go that down. Yeah. Okay.
Or maybe it's to get like way more usage
out of the because they they can capture
the market if they want to be like uh
60x uh cheaper than Opus.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And what they need is to
make sure that they get so much more
people using it to get better feedback.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And I mean with a cheaper the
cheap model like that then you can run
run faster. Yeah. That's interesting.
Uh cheap so cheaper than every other
agent scoring above 60 at the index.
Uh s cost quality parto frontier. Okay.
Medium effort per cost 1.24. 24 2.21 per
task high effort viant lens three
four point above at 4.10 and 482
uh major gain versus composer 2. Okay,
but I I'm not sure like how many people
are were using composer 2 like
>> I don't even know if people know what
composer 2 was because if they use
cursor you you you get the software and
you choose cloud code or codex. Yeah,
>> even on my timeline I don't see that
many people talking about composer.
>> Check that right now.
Composer
2.5
latest
uh crash coming. Okay.
Okay. Composite F. Oh, that's uh
uh I know why. Uh it's it's the model I
I'm using uh right now. Uh same as 4.7
and uh 50 uh 5.5
but cheapest. Yeah, faster but cheapest.
Uh cursor with the speed and quality of
composer 2.5 might be current aex of
coding with agent. Yeah, that's
interesting. What do you think of of
composer 2.5? So far
the architecture need to improve our
file and photo structure with a project.
Okay. I have used 17
uh 725 million composer 2.5 token almost
all via pi. Okay. And my pure size
extension especially great at
collaborative agent. Interesting.
Amazing at aentic code. Yeah. Okay.
That's cool. That could be a good
vertical for for um for composer and
cursor if they have yeah aentic coding
mean like you have multiple agent at the
same time that working in a project
could be cool uh hest and let it close
more effective alternative open
really good some forget simple things
like important statement
capable
It's better than collect for UI
instruction and use of skill but still
behind OP.
Yeah. I mean like the guy from Yo
with 50
is he from No, he's not. Uh
100k views. So that's
>> that's not a lot.
>> Yeah, that's not nothing but that's not
crazy.
Is it is it trending?
Oh, that's us.
>> Oh, we are trending.
>> We're trending, bro. Ah, it's us. Let's
go. [laughter]
>> Uh, first task is pretty good for
composer 2.5.
Uh, that that's
cool. Oh, you don't see the price.
>> No, I don't see the Oh, yeah. That's
That's a big That's a 20x. Yeah,
that's good. And score 64 64 63 like for
what we do, I don't think we will see
that difference in term of reasoning.
>> No. And even if you just let it run
triple, it's still so much cheaper and
doing it triple times or having three
agents doing the same thing, comparing
them, merging it, that gives you a
better quality and so much cheaper.
>> Yeah. But c can you put that with MS
running away?
Okay, I'm using this day MS agent plus
grog.
I drop clone max. Okay.
Uh
can you
because if you can only use it I don't I
don't think you can use it on open
router right
>> they said not they said it was only on
cursor
>> composer
yeah
so
yeah I mean you I know Todd can uh you
can connect to a cursor via the IP
I think from one up to I don't know
exactly how it works but you can connect
to it but you use the the yeah you use
the cursor
CLI and maybe even like the cursor SDK
to connect to the composer too I don't
know
>> yeah but then the question also is
because it was Kimmy right that they
were using Yes.
>> If if they made actual changes to Kimmy
or if they just use that one and put
additional information on top with each
quest.
>> I think that's the error state, right?
What they do?
>> Yeah.
>> So they take it and then they they Yeah.
Ah they make a better airs
a
>> real life updates and uh and that's it.
>> Yeah. So that's also why it's not on the
on the on the
>> components list.
>> Uh among the far fest coding agent
composer 2.5 faster run an average wall
time of 16.7
minutes per task. The third fastest
agent and behind OPUS 4.7 and GPT5
medium. Okay.
GPT5.5 is not that crazy fast. No.
>> Uh, it is not, but still AI is so much
faster than we ever had, so who cares?
>> And fast mode enable better
responsiveness at 6x pricing. That's
cool.
>> Like, uh, 5.5 low fast is amazing. I
love it.
>> But it's bye-bye my subscription. But,
uh, yeah, good.
>> I don't use it. Yeah,
>> because I I'm just working with three
CLI, three different projects. So, I can
wait on the first one because I'm
already working in the second and third.
>> Yeah, makes sense. Uh, artificial
analysis encoding agent index. So, yeah,
that's the that's what we saw. So, yeah,
they leaprog that. It's cool. Opus 4.7.
Ah, yeah. Okay. So
that's the that's the where they called
it and CLI Opus 4.7 card. Okay. Oh yeah.
Medium. Okay. Okay. Okay. Uh artificial
analysis coding index versus cost per
task 4.5 codex.
Okay. Oh, they are the same. Okay. Cost
per task. Yeah. I mean Yeah. That's
good. That's really, really good.
You can even use that for on a 20 bucks
subscription. If you can't pay 200 bucks
a month and then you have a crazy good
model.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And for not for every
task need like a big model. A lot of
tasks are so simple to do.
>> And if it's fast, you just run it
multiple times. And that's why also it's
good aentic, right? Because uh yeah,
then you can run more in parallel. still
go with like the 200 subscription, but
then you uh Okay, that's interesting.
>> Yeah. And you just give each agent a
different task.
>> Yeah.
>> Like one needs to double check
everything
>> and needs to question everything and the
other one is for security and just have
them merge all the code and and
improvements that they can do.
>> That's that's
>> are you? Yeah. If you have something
like uh like for example you have a new
project you can run cursor agent
uh composer on on all of the GitHub task
and stuff you start bootstrapping and
then you pull everything you test
everything and then
>> yeah you can you can have like some good
asynchronous work job
on that
>> that can be a cheap good project a good
setup
>> that's cool uh score by benchmark okay
so that looks legit. I mean, would that
make you redownload Kyos?
>> Nope. [laughter]
>> Well, the only thing is every week we
have something new. So,
>> I want to see a big improvement in in
the output and now it's still behind GPT
5.5.
>> I am coding fast. I'm coding properly. I
don't have issues.
>> So, why should I swap? because I'm still
working way within my own budget.
>> Yeah. And that's going to be interesting
like because okay, one day we're going
to reach like a 99 uh percent in every
[__] benchmark whatsoever and getting
like the the 10 more like
0.1 point on whatever benchmark coding
whatever will not matter at all. So
everyone will have their own model. So
maybe they will we will stop swapping or
use both or whatever uh once we it will
be like maxed out.
>> Yeah. Then it's it's more about what is
the easiest to use and the most stable
product.
>> Exactly.
Yeah. And that's why I think like for
example like AMS
got um
got like open CL got lost a lot of user
get MS got a lot more and like have the
same uh growth similar to growth because
um it was way more stable and less than
a mess than open itself. So yeah, maybe
we can see the same kind of movement for
the models too.
>> Yeah, I think so. I think that's going
to matter a lot.
>> Yeah,
>> because if we go up a lot more in in in
points so that we go towards the 99,
I think the last points are only for
people who do the really complex work.
>> Yeah, we're gonna find vaccine against
cancer with like composer five. Yeah,
but people making WordPress templates
and and forms, they don't need it.
>> Yeah, true. I was thinking about that
like we do like get back to Shopify
e-commerce like uh drop shipping stuff
on Shopify.
>> Mhm.
>> And especially with like a Shopify CLI
with the model that we have now compared
to what we had like one year ago when we
started to look at it. Yeah, that
improved the entire game.
>> I mean, I'm probably not going to be the
the only one doing that and everyone on
Earth is doing the same [__] [__]
but uh like the game is probably way
more interesting right now.
>> Yes.
>> Uh so yeah, model detail uh uh reporting
cursor reporting 85% of total compute
for his own additional training open
weight compos. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So
continue training on moonshot AI open
weight Kimid 2.5 as with composer 2 with
cursor reporting 85% of total compute
from its own additional training and
reinforcement learning they are the only
one with this data that's why they got
bought by alen for 1060 billion
>> they tracked everything and I think
that's that's that's AI apps right now
like you need to track every action
every workflow because that's where the
data is and the more points you have.
That's where the value is and uh
>> it's all about data.
>> Yes. And more than ever.
>> Yes.
>> And it's same thing for content and like
Yeah. coding and stuff. Yeah. It's nuts.
Uh pricing 50 per 2.5. Yeah. Okay. And
stream 15. That's crazy for the fast
variant the default in cursor. Okay.
Available exclusive available
exclusively in cursor both cursor ID and
cursor CLI external is not available.
>> Yeah. You need to have the cursor rep.
>> Yeah. Cursor CLI too. Yeah. Okay. So if
you have the cursor CLI then you can in
that way it works like the T3 code front
end is using cursor CLI to use cursor
models uh in another interface.
>> Yeah but then it should also be possible
to set up an API call to your own Mac
mini and use the cursor CLI to get cheap
API.
>> Yeah, exactly. Oh,
>> just host it yourself.
>> Yeah,
nice.
Uh, learn more. Why not give me 2.5?
Okay. Reddit. Some feedback on Reddit.
Uh, composer 2.5 is my new default. It's
fast, accurate, and actually cheap.
Train myself to use GPT 5.5 for anything
that was not trivial.
Yeah.
Oops. Too much doom.
Doom.
Nope. Still too much doom.
Okay, good.
uh try component mostly because I was
scared and I didn't want to build bad
credit another fix this lint error loop
and it's good like it's annoying good I
know how fast it is stuff land stuff
lands in the right file doesn't reward
half of the module for no reason pick up
weird pattern without me pasting three
example every time it's not sitting
there and doing agent slop as much
uh it's fast which sound dumb until you
have been starting at the spinner
between 10 20 for on a refactor hi
and yeah chip I know it's that's boring
to post but uh when you are in C all day
and ups 5.5 habits get expensive fast
yeah
>> uh debating to switch to codex because I
use 5.5 most of the time but not the
cook with 2.5 con me to stay okay me too
cooked yeah it's all major influencer
uh
>> I think the only way to say it this to
see if people are still using it in
another week.
>> True.
I mean, it's been six days already.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What about now?
Very good version. No need for API since
it launched. That's no need for API call
since it launched. That's great. Takes
lower case. Whatever. Whatever.
Very class fast mode, but 15 output is
not exactly ship. Yeah, but you're in
fast mode, bro. Uh tag. I'm starting to
think discuss about marketing. Okay.
Okay. What about So we have been through
that composer benchmark pricing. We know
about that.
Cool. Cool. Cool. Alen uh Alen, we have
already been on it. Pricing on. That's
done. That's done. Open router. We know
it's on an open routter.
And I think that's it. It has been 42
minutes. Okay.
Uh, tech. So, yeah. Do you like cheap
and fast model?
>> It's looking good to be honest.
>> Yeah.
>> And if they really get those numbers in
the benchmark, then it it's good to try.
>> Yeah. But do you know if they uh
do you know if they have like the
API cost for example for codex and
entropic inside cursor or do we have
subscription pricing?
>> I don't know
>> because if it's API cost then if you use
opus 4.7 you're not going to use
composer 2.5 for long. No, but yeah, I'm
not using the cursor, but in my CLI, I'm
doing everything within my subscription.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I wouldn't even know why I want to
pay API cost.
>> Yeah. Oh, exactly. Okay. Yeah. for like
aentic but I mean like the it's coming
next months where like when they um when
entropic forbid uh to uh use
subscription in any other third part uh
parties front end
>> yeah except for CLI
>> no if it uh it has to be in the CLI for
on your computer but like for example in
ship code I can't use
The
>> Yeah. It's like every third party
service they treat as a API call.
>> Yes. Exactly.
>> Yeah.
>> Which is No. No. Not that.
>> No. That means people are not going to
use it because if you can do it for free
on Codex.
>> Exactly.
>> And even if it's cheap, you don't know
how much it's going to cost. It's always
a surprise.
>> Yeah. It's No, it's it's nuts. Like the
cost are not like Okay. So on my
subscription
uh
30. Okay. So no on this computer
last 30. Okay. So not okay. So it's not
in this computer but yeah I think I show
you right. It's on my dev computer. I
was like 5k a month for both codeex and
entropic. I sp like Yeah. Yeah. 10k and
I paid 400
>> for both together for what I consume in
token.
>> Yeah. So then it is actually a really
good pricing that we have in the
subscription price.
>> Yeah. And today and like
uh the tok the token are not moving the
usage is not moving.
>> Oh I didn't try it. I didn't track it.
>> Okay. Yeah. installed the Codex bar but
like a subscription or in pace right now
in pace which is good
>> that's perfect for us right
>> yeah oh yeah
uh yeah do I have any other stuff no I
think we talk about the benchmark and
stuff yeah so basically cheap and fast
uh western
uh I think that's it
okay I mean we Can I conclude already
with uh Yeah, we're not going to use it,
but thank you.
>> Yeah. Well, were you like at least
thinking about using it?
>> I mean, yeah, I was even thinking like
maybe I can get the 20 bucks
subscription so I can use cursor when I
completely out of uh open AI or code.
>> But like for this week, I think I'm
good. So plus especially but with the
codeex resetting like the subscription
every now and then.
>> Mhm.
>> It's happening every week almost or
every two three days. So
>> yeah if you use it at least only for uh
checking the code that was created by
codeex you can take out the opus throw
it away take the cheaper one and have
that used.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And try try compos.
>> That will save you some money. But I'm
not I have a working setup. I'm happy
with the pricing and they didn't
convince me yet to swap.
>> Yeah, I mean
I I will try for you 20 bucks and then I
will tell you. Oh, whoa.
>> Use it. Use it.
>> And hi Michael. Michael. Hi.
Hi. Yeah. Michael. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi guy.
But uh Yeah. Okay. So, I think that's
it.
>> Yeah. That that was a good one.
>> Yeah. Thank you, Ker. Uh if you want to
sponsor us because we said that your
model are great, please send us a check.
We take crypto. [laughter]
But uh okay, thank you. And Michael, if
you want to subscribe to the channel and
come back next week, that would be sick.
And the video of the recap of this mod
of this uh live stream will be posted in
the next few days. Uh, Mitchell, thank
you so much for your time and
>> thank you too.
>> We will see you around. Bye. Bye.